<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Japan Candles</string>
   
    <string name="list_hammer">Hammer</string>
    <string name="list_hanging_man">Hanging man</string>
    <string name="list_bullish_engulfing">Bullish engulfing</string>
    <string name="list_bearish_engulfing">Bearish engulfing</string>
    <string name="list_dark_cloud_cover">Dark-cloud cover</string>
    <string name="list_piercing_pattern">Piercing pattern</string>
    <string name="list_morning_star">Morning star</string>
    <string name="list_evening_star">Evening star</string>
    <string name="list_abandoned_baby">Abandoned baby</string>
    <string name="list_belt_hold_line">Belt-hold line</string>
    <string name="list_advance_block">Advance block</string>
    <string name="list_harami">Harami</string>
    <string name="list_harami_cross">Harami cross</string>
    <string name="list_inverted_hammer">Inverted hammer</string>
    <string name="list_mat_hold_pattern">Mat-hold pattern</string>
    <string name="list_one_neck_line">One-neck line</string>
    <string name="list_shooting_star">Shooting star</string>
    <string name="list_stalled_pattern">Stalled pattern</string>
    <string name="list_tasuki_gaps">Tasuki gaps</string>
    <string name="list_three_crows">Three crows</string>
    <string name="list_three_methods">Three methods</string>
    <string name="list_window">Window</string>
    
    <string name="details_back">Back</string>
    
    <string name="eula_title">License</string>
	<string name="eula_accept">Accept</string>
	<string name="eula_refuse">Refuse</string>
    
    <string name="details_html_header"><![CDATA[
        <html>
		<head>	
			<style type="text/css">
				img { float: left; padding-right: 3px; padding-bottom: 3px; }
				img.rht { float: right; padding-left: 3px; padding-bottom: 3px; padding-top: 3px }
				p { text-align: justify; font-size: 16pt; }
			</style>
		<head>
		<body>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="details_html_footer"><![CDATA[
        </body>
        </html>
    ]]></string>    
    
    <string name="details_hammer"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Hammer</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/hammer_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Hammer</i> — an important bottoming candlestick line. The hammer and the hanging man are both the same line, that is a small real body (green 
       		or red) at the top of the session\'s range and a very long lower shadow with little or no upper shadow. When this line appears during 
       		a downtrend it becomes a bullish hammer. For a classic hammer, the lower shadow should be at least twice the height of the real body.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_hanging_man"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Hanging man</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/hanging_man_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Hanging man</i> — an important top reversal. The hanging man and the hammer are both the same type of candlestick line (i.e, a small real body (green or red), 
       		with little or no upper shadow, at the top of the session\'s range and a very long lower shadow). But when this line appears during an uptrend, it becomes a 
       		bearish hanging man. It signals the market has become vulnerable, but there should be bearish confirmation the next session (i.e., a red candlestick session with a 
       		lower close or a weaker opening) to signal a top. In principle, the hanging man\'s lower shadow should be two or three times the height of the real body.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_bullish_engulfing"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Bullish engulfing</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/bullish_engulfing_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Bullish engulfing</i> — pattern is comprised of a large green real body which engulfs a small red real body in a downtrend. The bullish engulfing pattern 
       		is an important bottom reversal.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_bearish_engulfing"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Bearish engulfing</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/bearish_engulfing_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Bearish engulfing</i> — a major top reversal pattern, occurs when selling pressure overwhelms buying pressure as reflected by a long red real 
       		body engulfing a small green real body in an uptrend.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_dark_cloud_cover"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Dark cloud cover</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/dark_cloud_cover_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Dark-cloud cover</i> — a bearish reversal signal. In an uptrend a long green candlestick is followed by a red candlestick that opens above the 
       		prior green candlestick\'s high. It then closes well into the green candlestick\'s real body.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_piercing_pattern"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Piercing pattern</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/piercing_pattern_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Piercing pattern</i> — a bottom reversal signal. In a downtrend, a long red candlestick is followed by a gap lower during the next session. 
       		This session finishes as a strong green candlestick which closes rnove than halfway into the prior red candlestick\'s real body. 
       		Compare to the on-neck line, the in-neck line, and the thrusting line.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_morning_star"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Morning star</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/morning_star_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Morning star</i> — a major bottom reversal pattern formed by three candlesticks. The first is a long red real body, the second is a small real body 
       		(green or red) which gaps lower to form a star, the third is a green candlestick that closes well into the first session\'s red real body.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_evening_star"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Evening star</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/evening_star_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Evening star</i> — a major top reversal pattern formed by three candlesticks. The first is a tall green real body, the second is a small real body (green or red) 
       		which gaps higher to form a star, the third is a red candlestick which closes well into the first session\'s green real body.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_abandoned_baby"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Abandoned baby</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/abandoned_baby_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Abandoned baby</i> — a very rare major top or bottom reversal signal. 
       		It is comprised of a doji star which gaps away (including shadows) from the prior and following 
       		session\'s candlesticks.
       	</p>
       	<p>
       		<img alt="dsf" src=\'file:///android_asset/abandoned_baby1_128.png\' class=\'rht\'/> 
       		The same as a Western island top or bottom in which the island session is also a doji.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_advance_block"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Advance block</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/advance_block_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Advance block</i> — a variation on three green soldiers in which the last two soldiers (i.e., green real bodies) display weakening upside drive. 
       		This weakness could be in the form of tall upper shadows or progressively smaller real bodies. It signifies a diminution of buying force or an increase in selling pressure.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_belt_hold_line"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Belt-hold line</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/belt_hold_line_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Belt-hold line</i> — there are bullish and bearish belt holds. A bullish belt hold is a tall green candlestick that opens on its low. It is also called a green opening shaven bottom. 
       		At a low price area, this is a bullish signal. A bearish belt hold is a long red candlestick which opens on its high. Also referred to as a red opening shaven head. 
       		At a high price level, it is considered bearish.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_harami"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Harami</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/harami_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Harami</i> — a two candlestick pattern in which a small real body holds within the prior session\'s unusually large real body. The harami 
       		implies the immediately preceding trend is concluded and that the bulls and bears are now in a state of truce.
       	</p>
       	<p>
       		<img alt="dsf" src=\'file:///android_asset/harami1_128.png\' class=\'rht\'/> 
       		The color of the second real body can be green or red. Most often the second real body is the opposite color of the first real body.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_harami_cross"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Harami cross</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/harami_cross_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Harami cross</i> — a harami with a doji on the second session instead of a small real body. An important top (bottom) reversal signal especially after a 
       		tall green (red) candlestick line.
       	</p>
       	<p>
       		<img alt="dsf" src=\'file:///android_asset/harami_cross1_128.png\' class=\'rht\'/> 
       		It is also called a petrifying pattern.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_inverted_hammer"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Inverted hammer</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/inverted_hammer_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Inverted hammer</i> — following a downtrend, this is a candlestick line that has a long upper shadow and a small real body at the lower end of 
       		the session. There should be no, or very little, lower shadow. It has the same shape as the bearish shooting star, but when this line occurs 
       		in a downtrend, it is a bullish bottom reversal signal with confirmation the next session (i.e., a green candlestick with a higher close or a higher opening).
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_mat_hold_pattern"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Mat-hold pattern</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/mat_hold_pattern_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Mat-hold pattern</i> — a bullish continuation pattern. A green candlestick is followed by a small red real body which gaps higher. Then there are two small red candlesticks 
       		which are followed by a strong green candlestick (or a candlestick which gaps open above the last red candlestick).
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_one_neck_line"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>One-neck line</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/one_neck_line_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>On-neck line</i> — a red candlestick in a downtrend is followed by a small green candlestick whose close is near the low of the session of the red candlestick. 
       		It is a bearish continuation pattern. The market should continue to move lower after the green candlestick\'s low is broken. 
       		Compare to an in-neck line, a thrusting line, and a piercing pattern.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_shooting_star"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Shooting star</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/shooting_star_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Shooting star</i> — a candlestick with a long upper shadow with little, or no lower shadow, and a small real body near the lows of the session that arises after an uptrend. 
       		It is a bearish candlestick signal in an uptrend.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_stalled_pattern"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Stalled pattern</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/stalled_pattern_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Stalled pattern</i> — a small green real body which is either above the prior stalled Pattern long green real body or near its top. Sometimes there is a short green candlestick 
       		before the lone green one. At the emergence of the stalled pattern, the market\'s rally should stall. Also called a deliberation pattern.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_tasuki_gaps"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Tasuki gaps</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/tasuki_gaps1_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Tasuki gaps</i> — there are downside and upside tasuki gaps. The downside tasuki gap is formed when, in a declining market, a red real body gaps lower. 
       		This candlestick is followed by a green candlestick, of about the same size, which opens in the red session\'s real body and then closes above the red\'s real body. 
       		It is a bearish continuation pattern.
       	</p>
       	<p>
       		<img alt="dsf" src=\'file:///android_asset/tasuki_gaps_128.png\' class=\'rht\'/> 
       		The upside tasuki gap is a bullish continuation pattern. It is formed when a green candlestick which gaps higher is followed by a red candlestick of about the same 
       		size which opens within the green real body and closes under the green\'s real body. Tasuki gaps are rare.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_three_crows"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Three crows</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/three_crows_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Three crows</i> — three relatively long consecutive red candlesticks which close near or on their lows. A top reversal at a high price level or after an extended rally.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_three_methods"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Three methods</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/three_methods_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Three methods</i> — there are two types. The first is the falling three methods which is a bearish continuation pattern. It is comprised of five lines. 
       		A long red real body is followed by three small, usually green, real bodies which hold within the first session\'s range. 
       		Then a red candlestick closes at a new low for the move.
       	</p>
       	<p>
       		<img alt="dsf" src=\'file:///android_asset/three_methods1_128.png\' class=\'rht\'/> 
       		The second is the rising three methods which is a bullish continuation pattern. A tall green candlestick preceded three small, 
       		usually red, real bodies that hold within the green candlestick\'s range. 
       		The fifth line of this pattern is a strong green candlestick that closes at a new high for the move.
       	</p>
	]]></string>
	
    <string name="details_window"><![CDATA[
       	<h1>Window</h1>
       	<p>
       		<img src=\'file:///android_asset/window_128.png\'/> 
       		<i>Window</i> — the same as a Western gap. Windows are continuation patterns. When the market rallies and opens a window, there should be a pullback to that window. 
       		The window should be support.
       	</p>
       	<p>
       		<img alt="dsf" src=\'file:///android_asset/window1_128.png\' class=\'rht\'/> 
       		The window should be support. If a window opens in a selloff, there should be a rally to the window. The window should be resistance. The Japanese expression is that 
       		"the market goes to the window."
       	</p>
	]]></string>

</resources>